https://www.nzweddingdirectory.co.nz/pages/privacy-policy.html

Honeymoon Destinations NZ
Honeymoon Destinations Int.
Honeymoon Destinations NZ
Honeymoon Destinations Int.
Search
Privacy PolicyWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:• To process transactions Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.  • To send periodic emailsNote: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can do so by following the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email, or by emailing us with 'unsubscribe' in the subject..Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.nzweddingdirectory.co.nz/page/terms-of-trade.htmlYour ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
Instagram
Follow us on Instagram
Locations
NorthlandAucklandWaiheke IslandGreat Barrier IslandCoromandelWaikatoBay of PlentyRotoruaCentral Plateau / TaupoGisborneHawkes BayTaranakiPalmerston NorthManawatu/WanganuiWairarapaWellingtonMarlboroughNelsonWest CoastCanterburyTimaru/TwizelOamaruOtagoQueenstown/WanakaSouthlandNational NZ /
Online ShopsNorfolk IslandNew South Wales, AUSQueensland, AUSSouth Australia, AUSWestern Australia, AUSVictoria, AUSInternationalBooksE-BooksArticlesResources
Categories
AccommodationBooksE-BooksBridal Hair and Wedding MakeupBridal Dresses and Wedding AccessoriesCatering CompaniesDecorations and FavoursElopementsEntertainmentFlorists Gifts and RegistriesHealth and FitnessHire EquipmentHoneymoon Destinations NZHoneymoon Destinations Int.JewellersLimo Hire and Wedding TransportationMarriage CelebrantsMenswearPackagesPhoto and Video BoothsResourcesStag Do and Hen's NightWedding CakesWedding Invites & StationeryWedding PhotographersWedding PlannersWedding VenuesWedding VideographersWedding Shows
For Brides and Grooms
Log in or Register
Website Features
Listings & Advertising
The NZ Wedding Directory has been helping couples plan their weddings in NZ & Australia since 2002.
Our aim is to provide couples with the largest online wedding and honeymoon directory in NZ.
There are a number of options for adding your business to the New Zealand Wedding Directory.
Browse our options or contact us to see how we can help you make the most of your online advertising. We also have a number of banner options available.
Add a Listing
Banner Advertising
Terms of trade
Help
Your best Listing
Credits
Home page & banner photography bySephory Photography
About us
All content © New Zealand Wedding Directory. Powered by Envy Web+Design
